[
  { "id": 221, "question": "null", "answer": "zero" },
  { "id": 222, "question": "eins", "answer": "one" },
  { "id": 223, "question": "zwei", "answer": "two" },
  { "id": 224, "question": "drei", "answer": "three" },
  { "id": 225, "question": "vier", "answer": "four" },
  { "id": 226, "question": "fünf", "answer": "five" },
  { "id": 227, "question": "sechs", "answer": "six" },
  { "id": 228, "question": "sieben", "answer": "seven" },
  { "id": 229, "question": "acht", "answer": "eight" },
  { "id": 230, "question": "neun", "answer": "nine" },
  { "id": 231, "question": "zehn", "answer": "ten" },
  { "id": 232, "question": "elf", "answer": "eleven" },
  { "id": 233, "question": "zwölf", "answer": "twelve" },
  { "id": 234, "question": "dreizehn", "answer": "thirteen" },
  { "id": 235, "question": "vierzehn", "answer": "fourteen" },
  { "id": 236, "question": "fünfzehn", "answer": "fifteen" },
  { "id": 237, "question": "sechzehn", "answer": "sixteen" },
  { "id": 238, "question": "siebzehn", "answer": "seventeen" },
  { "id": 239, "question": "achtzehn", "answer": "eighteen" },
  { "id": 240, "question": "neunzehn", "answer": "nineteen" },
  { "id": 241, "question": "zwanzig", "answer": "twenty" },
  { "id": 242, "question": "dreißig", "answer": "thirty" },
  { "id": 243, "question": "vierzig", "answer": "forty" },
  { "id": 244, "question": "fünfzig", "answer": "fifty" },
  { "id": 245, "question": "sechzig", "answer": "sixty" },
  { "id": 246, "question": "siebzig", "answer": "seventy" },
  { "id": 247, "question": "achtzig", "answer": "eighty" },
  { "id": 248, "question": "neunzig", "answer": "ninety" },
  { "id": 249, "question": "hundert", "answer": "one hundred" },
  { "id": 250, "question": "tausend", "answer": "one thousand" },
  { "id": 251, "question": "rot", "answer": "red" },
  { "id": 252, "question": "blau", "answer": "blue" },
  { "id": 253, "question": "grün", "answer": "green" },
  { "id": 254, "question": "gelb", "answer": "yellow" },
  { "id": 255, "question": "schwarz", "answer": "black" },
  { "id": 256, "question": "weiß", "answer": "white" },
  { "id": 257, "question": "grau", "answer": "gray" },
  { "id": 258, "question": "braun", "answer": "brown" },
  { "id": 259, "question": "orange", "answer": "orange" },
  { "id": 260, "question": "rosa", "answer": "pink" },
  { "id": 261, "question": "lila", "answer": "purple" },
  { "id": 262, "question": "beige", "answer": "beige" },
  { "id": 263, "question": "hell", "answer": "light (color)" },
  { "id": 264, "question": "dunkel", "answer": "dark (color)" },
  { "id": 265, "question": "bunt", "answer": "colorful" },
  { "id": 266, "question": "der Tag", "answer": "day" },
  { "id": 267, "question": "die Woche", "answer": "week" },
  { "id": 268, "question": "der Monat", "answer": "month" },
  { "id": 269, "question": "das Jahr", "answer": "year" },
  { "id": 270, "question": "heute", "answer": "today" },
  { "id": 271, "question": "gestern", "answer": "yesterday" },
  { "id": 272, "question": "morgen", "answer": "tomorrow" },
  { "id": 273, "question": "jetzt", "answer": "now" },
  { "id": 274, "question": "dann", "answer": "then" },
  { "id": 275, "question": "bald", "answer": "soon" },
  { "id": 276, "question": "immer", "answer": "always" },
  { "id": 277, "question": "oft", "answer": "often" },
  { "id": 278, "question": "manchmal", "answer": "sometimes" },
  { "id": 279, "question": "selten", "answer": "rarely" },
  { "id": 280, "question": "nie", "answer": "never" },
  { "id": 281, "question": "früh", "answer": "early" },
  { "id": 282, "question": "spät", "answer": "late" },
  { "id": 283, "question": "der Morgen", "answer": "morning" },
  { "id": 284, "question": "der Vormittag", "answer": "before noon" },
  { "id": 285, "question": "der Mittag", "answer": "noon" },
  { "id": 286, "question": "der Nachmittag", "answer": "afternoon" },
  { "id": 287, "question": "der Abend", "answer": "evening" },
  { "id": 288, "question": "die Nacht", "answer": "night" },
  { "id": 289, "question": "Montag", "answer": "Monday" },
  { "id": 290, "question": "Dienstag", "answer": "Tuesday" },
  { "id": 291, "question": "Mittwoch", "answer": "Wednesday" },
  { "id": 292, "question": "Donnerstag", "answer": "Thursday" },
  { "id": 293, "question": "Freitag", "answer": "Friday" },
  { "id": 294, "question": "Samstag", "answer": "Saturday" },
  { "id": 295, "question": "Sonntag", "answer": "Sunday" },
  { "id": 296, "question": "Januar", "answer": "January" },
  { "id": 297, "question": "Februar", "answer": "February" },
  { "id": 298, "question": "März", "answer": "March" },
  { "id": 299, "question": "April", "answer": "April" },
  { "id": 300, "question": "Mai", "answer": "May" }
]
